var questions = [
    {
        question: "_____ is the process of finding and fixing errors within a given program.",
        choices: ["Scanning", "Executing", "Compiling", "Debugging"],
        answer: "Debugging"
    },

    {
        question: "In Java, which of the followning is an array",
        choices: ["Primitive data type", "Object References", "Objects", "None of the above"],
        answer: "Objects"
    },

    {
        question: "What is the correct definition of a package?",
        choices: ["A package is a collection of classes and interfaces", "A package is a collectin of classes", 
                  "A package is a collection of editing tools", "A package is a collection of interfaces"],
        answer: "A package is a collection of classes and interfaces"
    },

    {
        question: "Which is the correct way to declare core methods in Java?",
        choices: ["Comparator", "Set", "Collection", "EventListener"],
        answer: "Collection"
    },

    {
        question: "What does the abbreviation HTML stand for?",
        choices: ["HighText Markup Language", "HyperText Markup Language", "HyperText Markdown Language", "None of the above"],
        answer: "HyperText Markup Language"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is the smallest header in HTML by default?",
        choices: ["h2", "h1", "h4", "h6"],
        answer: "h6"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following does not require a closing tag?",
        choices: ["<br>", "<hr>", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        answer: "Both A and B"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following attributes is utilized to provide a unique name to an HTML element?",
        choices: ["type", "class", "id", "None of the above"],
        answer: "id"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following tags is utilized to render an image on a webpage?",
        choices: ["image", "img", "src", "None of the above"],
        answer: "img"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following tags is utilized to show the page's start and endpoints?",
        choices: ["<body>", "<doctype>", "<head>", "<html>"],
        answer: "<html>"
    }

];